idownloadall.com 2010-12-26

# Download the Latest Software, Games, DVD Movies, Music, TV Shows and ebooks! - iDownloadAll.com

**Our Commitment to Privacy**  
As a service provider and software producer, we know that you care about how your information is used and shared. We respect your right to privacy. Your ability to make informed choices about the use of your information is important to us. We want to make sure that you understand the type of information we collect about you, how it is used and the safeguards we use to protect it. This Privacy Policy explains our policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of personal information you share with us.

**The Information We Collect:**  
In browsing our site or when you interact with our website we may maintain a record of the following types of information. 

Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address or other technical information such as a referring web site, if any, and the path you take through our site when you visit us online. Your IP address is collected for the purpose of tracking. The date and time, the internet address of the website from which you link directly to our website. The browser you use to access our website. 

Only if, and when you decide to register and order products or subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials, some additional information might be collected, including: First Name, Last Name, Address, Zip/Postal, City, State, Country, Email, membership type. 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the totality of pages of this website.

**The Way We Use Information:**  
All information is stored in a secure database. 

The personal information we collect is generally used to process your requests and transactions, to provide you with high quality service, to customize your experience on our site and to understand your needs so that we may provide you with the most suitable products and services, allow you to purchase and download products, obtain access to services or otherwise engage in activities you select, help you quickly find software, services, or product information important to you, or notify you about changes to our service.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Consent**  
By providing us with your personal information when registering at our Site or when you obtain or use any of our products or services, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure by us of your personal information as provided in this Privacy Policy. 

Your consent includes the retention of personal information that is collected through our Site, including your personal information that you submit through a registration process, for as long as you are registered at our Site or you are a user of our products and services, and for a reasonable time thereafter, unless and until you withdraw your consent.

**Security**  
We are committed to maintaining the security of information under our control. We have taken security measures, consistent with industry practices, to protect your personal information. To try to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information, we have put in place industry-accepted physical, technical and administrative practices to safeguard and secure the information we collect. 

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. To protect the confidentiality of this category of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. If other people have access to your e-mail, they may be able to change information about your user profile. You should not use an e-mail account operated by an employer because many employers have the legal right to access such e-mail accounts. If you share a computer with anyone, always log out before leaving our Site to protect access to your information from subsequent users. 

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Credit card information is transmitted using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption. We use industry-accepted encryption to enhance the security of data transmissions and have implemented commercially available technologies to guard against unauthorized access to any personal information that is stored electronically by us. We restrict access to personal information about you to those employees who need to know the information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. 

Unfortunately, no transmission of information over the internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to our Site from your PC or the Internet Service Provider, and any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to ensure its security on our system and to try to prevent unauthorized access. 

**Links to Other Companies**  
Periodically, our Site may contain links to and from websites of our business partners, distributors, resellers, advertisers or other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies which you should read before you submit any personal data to these websites. We disclaim any liability for the data processing activities of our business partners, distributors and resellers, all of which act as independent data processing controllers. 

**Children**  
We encourage parents to take an active interest in their children's use of the Internet. Our Site is not targeted to children younger than 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect or store information of children younger than 13. Visitors who are under the age of 13 may use our Site only with the supervision and consent of a parent or guardian. None of the products or services available through Our Site may be purchased by anyone less than 18 years of age.

**Changes of Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. However, we will alert you that changes have been made by indicating at the top of the Privacy Policy the date it was last updated. If we ever make a material change to how we use the information you provide and the new uses are unrelated to uses we disclose in this Policy, we will communicate the changes in a prominent notice on our Site prior to its implementation and provide you the opportunity to change your marketing preferences to opt-out of such use. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**  
We strive to maintain the accuracy of the information collected through our Site. Furthermore, we believe that the individual is invaluable in ensuring that data is complete and accurate. We will provide you with access to personally identifiable information you provide through our Site for as long as we maintain that information in a readily accessible format. Similarly, we permit and encourage you to correct inaccuracies in the information you submit to us through our Site. If you believe that we do not have your current personal information, you can update it by contacting the [Customer Support Services](). 

If you have provided personal information to us, you may ask us to advise you of the scope of information our group processes about you, the purpose and nature of the processing and the recipients of the information.

**Language**  
This Privacy Policy was originally prepared in the English language. Although we may provide one or more translations for your convenience, the English version will control in the case of any conflict or discrepancy. 

**How To Contact Us:**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [Customer Support]().
